Guide to the Group Material Archive 1976-2009 (bulk 1979-1996) MSS 215
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Oversize Series III: Press and Promotional Material
  - "AIDS Timeline" - Press - The Daily Californian, November 10, 1989 (Box 50, Folder 24)
  - Press - Cooper Pioneer, April 29, 1982 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Article- Getting Ready for the Golden Eighties: A Conversation with Chantal Akerman by Gary Indiana, 1983 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Press - Chicago Catolico, February 1990 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Press - Oberlin College Observer, October 25, 1990 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - "Confronting the AIDS Epidemic" - Newspaper, 1990-1991 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Article from New York Times Magazine - Style by Mary Jo Salter, July 17, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Press - "Americana" - Almost Home by Lisa Liebmann, undated (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Press Art Worker's Coalition articles - Art's magazine, 1970 (Box 57, Folder 22)
- Oversize Series VI: Photographic Material
  This series contains oversize materials from Series VI: Photographic Material. This series includes photographs originally exhibited in Group Material projects.
  - "Luchar!" - photographs - 1 of 9, 1982 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - "Luchar!" - photographs - 2 of 9, 1982 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - "Luchar!" - photographs - 3 of 9, 1982 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - "Luchar!" - photographs - 4 of 9, 1982 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - "Luchar!" - photographs - 5 of 9, 1982 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - "Luchar!" - photographs - 6 of 9, 1982 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - "Luchar!" - photographs - 7 of 9, 1982 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - "Luchar!" - photographs - 8 of 9, 1982 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - "Luchar!" - photographs - 9 of 9, 1982 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - "Pity Puppy", 1983 (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - "Democracy Poll" - Black and white prints, 1990 (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - Nancy Linn- Matted photograph - 1 of 2, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Nancy Linn- Matted photograph - 2 of 2 - inscription to Felix from Julie, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 14)
- Oversize Series X: Objects
  This series contains oversize materials from Series X: Objects
  - "Market" - [Exhibited Material] - Bunting (flags), 1995 (Box 53, Object ID: 215.2.0058)
- Accretions 2009: Series XI: "Vital Archive"
  The materials in this series were compiled by Sabrina Locks for her curated exhibition "Vital Archive: Revisiting Group Material's AIDS Timeline," which took place in the Spring of 2009 at the Bard Center for Curatorial Studies. They were added to the collection with the permission of the donor.
  - Vital Archive | Revisiting Group Material's AIDS Timeline Materials, 2009 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Vital Archive, [2009] (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Aids Timeline Color Copies-Vital Archive, [2009] (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Vital Archive, [2009] (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Vital Archive, [2009] (Box 56, Folder 5)